# EMILY HILL

## Full Stack Developer

## CONTACT

(713) 854-6831 emhillmed2O21@gmail.com https://github.com/emsaw721

## EDUCATION

#### CODING BOOTCAMP

Rice Univeristy

Aug. 2022- Feb. 2023

#### POST-BAC PRE-MED

Fordham University

Sept. 2016- May 2020

#### B.A. ENGLISH

Fordham University

Aug. 2012 - May 2016

#### SKILLS

Content Writing

Front End(CSS, HTML, JavaScript)
Back End (Node.js, Express, SQL,

MongoDB)

Laboratory Methods

Science Research

Literary Research

## SUMMARY

I am a science enthusiast, literary lover, and new full stack developer. I am proficient in many technologies, but specialize in the MERN stack. I addition to my coding experience, I have a background in both scientific and literary research.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### NURSING ASSISTANT

St. John's Riverside Hospital

April 2020 - July 2020

• Assisted nursing staff during the COVID-19 pandemic.

#### LITERARY INTERN

America Media

## May 2019- September 2019

- Created original content for online and print publications.
- Assisted with research.

## AUTOPSY, TOXICOLOGY, & HISTOLOGY LAB ASSISTANT

Erie County Medical Examiner's Office

## June 2015 - September 2015

- I assisted the forensic pathologists with autopsies including recording weights and assisting with simple procedures.
- I assisted the toxicology and histology labs collecting and storing specimens, reviewing lab procedures, and stored specimens for future review.